{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269269319","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269269319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 97098edd-6e9f-48ea-ae97-7402eea57523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ko.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" msisimko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269278102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269278102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269281074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269281073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gingile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GINGILE"," userResponse":" GINGILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269284288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269284288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269287488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269287488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mishale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISHALE"," userResponse":" MISHALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269290601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269290601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" LELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269293679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269293679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nywele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269296746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269296746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILE"," userResponse":" ZILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269299757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269299757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269302903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269302903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269305800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269305799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polepole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" POLEPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269309415","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269309415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" polepole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269309497","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269309497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polepole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" POLEPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269314783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269314783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d575eda3-8e1b-4ace-b5fb-380ac928b37f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.le.rand.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" polepole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269329280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269329280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kale_kuni-mali-kale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kale"," userResponse":" kale"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269338050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269338049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pole_elsa-jona-pole"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pole"," userResponse":" pole"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269347108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269347108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vile_mbao-vile-damu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vile"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269362154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269362154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vile_kapu-vile-wivu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vile"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269374866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269374866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yule_miti-aina-yule"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yule"," userResponse":" yule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269387683","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269387683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kule_miye-naro-kule"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kule"," userResponse":" kule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269399178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269399178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lele_nazi-lele-vita"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lele"," userResponse":" lele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269409140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269409140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tule_yenu-tule-kata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tule"," userResponse":" tule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269439901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269439901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lele_tani-mkia-lele"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lele"," userResponse":" lele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269448081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269448081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tule_mbwa-tule-humu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tule"," userResponse":" tule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269453822","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269453821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tule_mbwa-tule-humu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269463305","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269463305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" d049c989-bd0c-4a3f-9149-7d360484a419"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tule_mbwa-tule-humu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269477892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269477892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tule_mbwa-tule-humu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tule"," userResponse":" tule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269486023","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269486023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tule_yenu-tule-kata"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tule"," userResponse":" tule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269494163","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269494163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lele_nazi-lele-vita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lele"," userResponse":" lele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269505459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269505459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vile_kapu-vile-wivu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vile"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269513841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269513841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lele_tani-mkia-lele"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lele"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269523367","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269523367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lele_tani-mkia-lele"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lele"," userResponse":" lele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269533498","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269533498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pole_elsa-jona-pole"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pole"," userResponse":" pole"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269551182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269551182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kule_miye-naro-kule"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kule"," userResponse":" kule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269572728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269572728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yule_miti-aina-yule"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yule"," userResponse":" yule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269581463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269581462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vile_mbao-vile-damu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vile"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269590187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269590186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kale_kuni-mali-kale"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kale"," userResponse":" kale"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269595936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269595932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kale_kuni-mali-kale"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269601961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269601960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" db393d68-1819-4856-ad7b-a1d0826d4998"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.show.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kale_kuni-mali-kale"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269612021","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269612021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269615413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269615413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269616983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269616982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269620452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269620452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269622029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269622029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269625565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269625565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269627130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269627130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALALE"," userResponse":" ALALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269630999","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269630999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269632553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269632553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269636987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269636987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269638708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269638708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nywele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269645131","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269645130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nywele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" START_NYWELE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269646086","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269646086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nywele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269647707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269647706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269653204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269653203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" START_VIDOLE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269655589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269655589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269657163","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269657163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mishale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISHALE"," userResponse":" MISHALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269663058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269663058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mishale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISHALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269664646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269664646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269667818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269667818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.le.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269669831","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269669830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269669994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269669994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269685094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269685094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 1a46b818-1d9a-4931-9ff3-c3ae6789cbfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.le.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269698466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269698466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kile_kile-baba-eupe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kile"," userResponse":" kile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269706323","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269706323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tele_tele-mguu-basi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tele"," userResponse":" tele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269714680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269714680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kile_zamu-kile-tena"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kile"," userResponse":" kile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269722281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269722281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pole_pole-lisa-kasa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pole"," userResponse":" pole"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269732764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269732764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pale_wetu-pale-kinu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pale"," userResponse":" pale"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269743436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269743436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_zile_waua-zile-gari"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zile"," userResponse":" zile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269751195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269751195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vile_vile-sifa-lako"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vile"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269760177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269760177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tele_kata-tupu-tele"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tele"," userResponse":" tele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269769570","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269769570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pole_nguo-pole-duni"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pole"," userResponse":" pole"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269777552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269777551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tele_mbio-tele-zuri"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tele"," userResponse":" tele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.noShow.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269783338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269783338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" c5d0856e-9f06-4e2f-a462-4f7a683902a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.le.noShow.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tele_mbio-tele-zuri"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269789755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269789755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" bbcb7887-b686-46e3-9f9e-109c93923502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269790070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269790070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" bbcb7887-b686-46e3-9f9e-109c93923502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269790208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269790208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" bbcb7887-b686-46e3-9f9e-109c93923502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269800997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269800996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gingile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GINGILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269802038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269802038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gingile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GINGILE"," userResponse":" GINGILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269807505","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269807505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269808544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269808544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269809804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269809804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269810843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269810842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yule"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269814764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269814763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kelele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269815810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269815810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kelele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269820401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269820401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269821448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269821447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269825790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269825789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makelele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269826830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269826830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makelele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKELELE"," userResponse":" MAKELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269830281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269830281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIALE"," userResponse":" MIALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269830735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269830735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269831472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269831472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" LELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269833725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269833725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269835631","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269835631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269836687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269836686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269840069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269840068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269841113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269841113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.le.rand.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269844833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269844833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269844998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269844998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269849933","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269849933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 988065b6-368c-40f0-bd8f-19217417bdc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.le.rand.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269859013","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269859013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" ca2e1d4a-64fa-4276-b9b8-6cde27709648"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" awali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269862375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269862374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" ca2e1d4a-64fa-4276-b9b8-6cde27709648"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAVULI"," userResponse":" MWAVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269865933","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269865933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" ca2e1d4a-64fa-4276-b9b8-6cde27709648"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" AKADELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269869148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269869147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" ca2e1d4a-64fa-4276-b9b8-6cde27709648"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269890939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269890938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" ca2e1d4a-64fa-4276-b9b8-6cde27709648"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269891039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269891039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" ca2e1d4a-64fa-4276-b9b8-6cde27709648"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269901437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269901437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 17b1e6d5-f380-46e2-8847-b7dd4e48201b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" awali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269904763","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269904762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 17b1e6d5-f380-46e2-8847-b7dd4e48201b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAVULI"," userResponse":" MWAVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269908271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269908271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 17b1e6d5-f380-46e2-8847-b7dd4e48201b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" AKADELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269911473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269911472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 17b1e6d5-f380-46e2-8847-b7dd4e48201b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269923902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269923901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 17b1e6d5-f380-46e2-8847-b7dd4e48201b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269924000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269924000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 17b1e6d5-f380-46e2-8847-b7dd4e48201b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269934076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269934076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 4d6bc8bc-3d5e-404b-8020-a4dc8228a52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" awali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269937401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269937400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 4d6bc8bc-3d5e-404b-8020-a4dc8228a52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAVULI"," userResponse":" MWAVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269940910","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269940910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 4d6bc8bc-3d5e-404b-8020-a4dc8228a52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" AKADELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269944064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269944063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 4d6bc8bc-3d5e-404b-8020-a4dc8228a52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270017333","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270017332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 4d6bc8bc-3d5e-404b-8020-a4dc8228a52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270025852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270025851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 4d6bc8bc-3d5e-404b-8020-a4dc8228a52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.li.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270031482","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270031481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 4d6bc8bc-3d5e-404b-8020-a4dc8228a52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270036517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270036516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 4d6bc8bc-3d5e-404b-8020-a4dc8228a52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.li.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pili pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270051749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270051749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bali_zamu-bali-boga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bali"," userResponse":" bali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270060783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270060783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_omba-kali-moyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270068907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270068907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bali_bali-mito-eupe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bali"," userResponse":" bali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270077391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270077391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_rudi-goli-nayo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goli"," userResponse":" goli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270086442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270086441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pili_sisa-pili-wapi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pili"," userResponse":" pili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270095225","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270095224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_moja-goli-jiji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goli"," userResponse":" goli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270103351","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270103351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_taja-goli-yadi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goli"," userResponse":" goli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270111937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270111937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pili_pili-heri-mpwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pili"," userResponse":" pili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270120130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270120130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pili_tuwe-pili-boma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pili"," userResponse":" pili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270129136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270129136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mali_mali-mate-nguo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mali"," userResponse":" mali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.show.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270134909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270134908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mali_mali-mate-nguo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270145053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270145053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 94a736ae-077b-4f6b-86ed-da5a5789989a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.show.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mali_mali-mate-nguo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270156115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270156115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukweli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" UKWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270159887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270159887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukweli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270161447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270161447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maswali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270165355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270165355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maswali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270166923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270166923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tafadhali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270171193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270171192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tafadhali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270172743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270172743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kivuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIVULI"," userResponse":" KIVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270176151","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270176151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kivuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIVULI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270177703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270177703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAROLI"," userResponse":" TAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270181301","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270181301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270182859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270182859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miwili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWILI"," userResponse":" MIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270187037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270187037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miwili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270188594","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270188594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" AKADELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270192273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270192273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270193834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270193834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270197073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270197072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270198626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270198626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umbali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270202241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270202241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umbali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270203797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270203797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270207539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270207539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270209551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270209550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270209667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270209667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270214879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270214878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270226678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270226677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270232451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270232451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 07ebece9-3056-45b6-b662-2a088a404335"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270232524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270232523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" f3de5588-ce28-4a3b-8c09-5830284d3d8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.li.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270244635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270244635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 738230a7-5644-48e7-9d2c-f92cb7ff15d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.li.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.li.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270245662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270245662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 738230a7-5644-48e7-9d2c-f92cb7ff15d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.li.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.li.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270249518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270249518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 738230a7-5644-48e7-9d2c-f92cb7ff15d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.li.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.li.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270249782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270249782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 738230a7-5644-48e7-9d2c-f92cb7ff15d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.li.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" swali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270250003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270250003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 738230a7-5644-48e7-9d2c-f92cb7ff15d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.li.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270255998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270255998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" 738230a7-5644-48e7-9d2c-f92cb7ff15d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.li.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" swali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270289969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270289968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270292753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270292753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270304264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270304264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270323328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270323328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270335387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270335386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270338164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270338163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270348947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270348946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270350565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270350565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270368458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270368458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270376079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270376079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270385776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270385775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270398623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270398623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270416040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270416040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270418646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270418645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270427800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270427800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270430174","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270430174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270440104","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270440104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270448182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270448181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270458176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270458176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270464196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270464196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270472158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270472158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270488261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270488261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270490458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270490458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270502740","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270502739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270504587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270504587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270514613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270514612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270522642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270522642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" fad4240c-93c2-4663-91b7-2b9800cf6a3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270537743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270537742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_jike-mama-lake"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270546096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270546096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_boma_boma-koti-yuko"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" boma"," userResponse":" boma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270554800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270554800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_rudi-miti-lima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lima"," userResponse":" lima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270564847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270564846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_juma_wali-mvua-juma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" juma"," userResponse":" juma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270573179","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270573179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_sasa-kama-jike"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kama"," userResponse":" kama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270582073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270582073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_dudu-mama-kuna"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270601161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270601161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_dudu-mama-kuna"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270610648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270610648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hema_hema-niwe-tani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hema"," userResponse":" hema"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270618718","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270618718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_hema_hema-niwe-tani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549270623689","data":{"timestamp":" 1549270623689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_113421"," gameId":" e5a1b3f0-db6c-4f9c-a7c1-1df5d6a4bf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_hema_hema-niwe-tani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}